Guide to the Records of Director of Academic Program Review, Barnett Hamberger 1972-2003 RG 9.7 RG 9.7
New York University Archives
Records of the Office of the Director of Academic Program Review (Barnett Hamberger)
1972-2003
RG 9.7
New York University Archives
99.0 linear feet (100 boxes)
This collection includes materials from the office of Barnett W. Hamberger, Director of Academic Program Review. The Office of Academic Affairs is responsible for new program registration with the New York State Education Department, as well as overseeing the academic affairs and compliance office serving the intercollegiate athletics program.
Hamberger, Barnett
Arrangement
Folders are arranged topically.
The files are grouped into 1 series:
I, Topical Files
Physical Access
Please note that this collection is stored offsite, and you must contact the repository to schedule access.
Separated Material
There is no information about materials that are associated by provenance to the described materials that have been physically separated or removed.
Scope and Content Note
The collection includes a variety of material about Coles Athletic Facilities, including budgets, advisory board reviews, student athlete information, athletic schedules, and awards. Also included in the records are accreditations, MSA reports, data surveys for various sectors of NYU, HEDS Reports, faculty resources network evaluation reports, and correspondence.
Please note: the contents of boxes 1, 2, 49, 56, 60, 67, 71, and 80 have been shifted to other boxes in the collection.
Historical/Biographical Note
Barnett W. Hamberger is an Assistant Chancellor at New York University and heads the Office of Academic Program Review. New York University's Office of Academic Program Review is responsible for new program registration with the New York State Education Department, as well as monitoring changes to currently registered programs; administering the University's compliance with the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act; and overseeing the academic affairs and compliance office serving the intercollegiate athletics program.
Mr. Hamberger has been at NYU since 1965 holding a variety of positions including Director of Branch Campus Affairs, Assistant to the Vice President for Academic Planning, Assistant Vice Chancellor for Student Affairs, and as a faculty member.
Access Restrictions
Institutional records of New York University are closed for a period of 20 years from the date of their creation (the date on which each document was written). Board of Trustees records are similarly closed for 35 years from the date of creation. The opening date for files spanning several years will be 20 years from the most recent date. Access will be given to material already 20 years old contained within a collection that is not yet open when such material can be isolated from the rest of the collection.
Materials related to personnel, faculty grievances, job searches and all files with information that falls under the University's Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (FERPA) policy are permanently restricted.
Please contact the University Archivists with specific questions regarding restrictions.
This collection is in
off-site storage
.
Provenance
This collection consists of multiple accessions from the Academic Program Review office.
Hamberger, Barnett; New York University.; Administrative records.; Correspondence.; New York (N.Y.); New York University |x Athletics.; Private universities and colleges |x Administration |y 20th century.; Reports.
- Series I
  - Statistics Committee, 1973-1979 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    General note
    3 1142 04058789 4
  - Statistics Committee, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Statistics Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Statistics Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Statistics Booklet, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Accreditation, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Accreditation, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Accreditation - Folder 1 of 2, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Accreditation - Folder 2 of 2, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Accreditation, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Accreditation, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Accreditation - Folder 1 of 2, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Accreditation - Folder 2 of 2, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Accreditation, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Doctoral Evaluations- Educational Sociology, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - NYS Doctoral Evaluations- Social Studies Ed., 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - NYS Doctoral Evaluations- Philosophy Of Education Re-Review, undated (Box 3, Folder 17)
    3 1142 04058800 9
  - NYS Doctoral Evaluations- Special Ed., 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - NYS Doctoral Evaluations- Secondary Ed., undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - NYS Doctoral Evaluations- Science Ed. - Folder 1 of 2, 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - NYS Doctoral Evaluations- Science Ed. - Folder 2 of 2, undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Doctoral Evaluations - Philosophy of Education, 1979-1982, 1985, undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - State Inventory - Education Doctoral Program, 1982, undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - NYS Doctoral Evaluations- Educational Sociology Revisit, 1984-1986 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - NYS Doctoral Evaluation- Health Ed. - Folder 1 of 2, 1981-1985, undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - NYS Doctoral Evaluation- Health Ed. - Folder 2 of 2, 1981-1985, undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Doctoral Review- General, 1982-1984, undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Doctoral Evaluation - Education Administration, 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - NYS Doctoral Evaluation- English Education, 1981-1982, undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Doctoral Evaluation- Higher Education- Folder 1 of 2, 1976, 1978-1982, undated (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Doctoral Evaluation- Higher Education- Folder 2 of 2, 1976, 1978-1982, undated (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Higher Education Re-Review - Folder 1 of 2, 1983-1985, undated (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Higher Education Re-Review - Folder 2 of 2, 1983-1985, undated (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - NYS Doctoral Evaluation- Elementary Education- Folder 1 of 2, 1980-1982, undated (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - NYS Doctoral Evaluation- Elementary Education- Folder 2 of 2, 1980-1982, undated (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - NYS Doctoral Evaluation- Art Education (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Doctoral Evaluation- Counselor Education, 1976, 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Doctoral Evaluation- Counselor Education, 1976, 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - NYS Doctoral Evaluation- Physical Ed.- Folder 1 of 2, 1981-1984, undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
    3 1142 04058791 0
  - NYS Doctoral Evaluation- Physical Ed.- Folder 2 of 2, 1981-1984, undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - NYS Doctoral Evaluation- Math Ed., 1976, 1979, 1981-1982, undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - NYS Doctoral Evaluation- Music Ed., 1981-1983, undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - NYS Doctoral Evaluation- History of Ed., 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - NYS Masters Degree Eval. 1972, 1972, undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - NYS Masters Degree Eval. 1973, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - NYS Masters Degree Eval. 1975, 1972, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - NYS Doctoral Project Council 1974, 1973-1974 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - NYS Doctoral Project Council 1975, 1974-1975, undated (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - NYS Doctoral Project Council 1977 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - NYS Doctoral Project General, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - NYS Doctoral Project General, 1976, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - NYS Doctoral Project- Anthropology, Economics, 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - NYS Doctoral Project- Chemistry, History, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - NYS Doctoral Project- Chemistry, History 1974- Folder 1 of 2, 1974-1975 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - NYS Doctoral Project- Chemistry, History 1974 - Folder 2 of 2, 1974-1975 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - NYS Doctoral Project- Chemistry, History, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - NYS Doctoral Project- English, Physics 1974 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - NYS Doctoral Project- English, Physics 1975- Folder 1 of 2, 1974-1975 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - NYS Doctoral Project- English, Physics 1975- Folder 2 of 2, 1974-1975 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - NYS Doctoral Project- French, Spanish, Portuguese, German, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - NYS Doctoral Project- French, Spanish, Portuguese, German 1975- Folder 1 of 3, 1975, undated (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - NYS Doctoral Project- French, Spanish, Portuguese, German 1975- Folder 2 of 3, 1975, undated (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - NYS Doctoral Project- French, Spanish, Portuguese, German 1975- Folder 3 of 3, 1975, undated (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - NYS Doctoral Project- French, Spanish, Portuguese, German 1976- Folder 1 of 3 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - NYS Doctoral Project- French, Spanish, Portuguese, German 1976- Folder 2 of 3 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - NYS Doctoral Project- French, Spanish, Portuguese, German 1976- Folder 3 of 3 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - NYS Doctoral Project- Philosophy, Slavic, Mathematics 1977 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - NYS Doctoral Project- Philosophy, Slavic, Mathematics 1976 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - NYS Doctoral Project- Philosophy, Slavic, Mathematics 1975 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - NYS Doctoral Project- Politics, Sociology 1977 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Consortium- Folder 1 of 2, 1971-1977, undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
    3 1142 04058790 2
  - Consortium- Folder 2 of 2, 1971-1977, undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - NYS Doctoral Project- Politics, Sociology- Folder 1 of 2, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - NYS Doctoral Project- Politics, Sociology- Folder 2 of 2, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Graduate Commission- Folder 1 of 2, 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Graduate Commission- Folder 2 of 2, 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Graduate Commission- Folder 1 of 2, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Graduate Commission- Folder 2 of 2, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Graduate Commission- Folder 1 of 2, 1978-1979 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Graduate Commission- Folder 2 of 2, 1978-1979 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Graduate Commission- Folder 1 of 2, 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Graduate Commission- Folder 2 of 2, 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Graduate Commission, 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - NYU Commission on Graduate Planning- Folder 1 of 2, 1974-1976, undated (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - NYU Commission on Graduate Planning- Folder 2 of 2, 1974-1976, undated (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Applied Science 1978, 1973-1974, 1978, 1981, undated (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Commission on Higher Ed. Connecticut, 1974, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Committee on Graduate and Professional Education Final Report, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - COGPE Interim Report and Summary, approximately 1974 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Doctor of Arts Degree- Folder 1 of 2, 1972, 1975-1977 1979-1981, undated (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Doctor of Arts Degree- Folder 2 of 2, 1972, 1975-1977 1979-1981, undated (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - NYU Finances- Folder 1 of 3, 1970, 1972-1973, 1975-1976, undated (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - NYU Finances- Folder 2 of 3, 1972-1973, 1975-1976 undated (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - NYU Finances- Folder 3 of 3, 1972-1973, 1975-1976 undated (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - NYU FInances, 1972, 1975-1976, undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Fudan University- Folder 1 of 2, 1980-1982, undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
    3 1142 04058792 8
  - Fudan University- Folder 2 of 2, 1980-1982, undated (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Long Island Report, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Nassau/Suffolk Counties Report, undated (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - NYS Doctoral Project- Anthropology, Economics 1978- Folder 1 of 2, 1978-1980 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - NYS Doctoral Project- Anthropology, Economics 1978- Folder 2 of 2, 1978-1980 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Self-Evaluation of the Doctoral Program in Human Relations, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - NYS Doctoral Project- Psychology- Folder 1 of 4, 1982-1986, undated (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - NYS Doctoral Project- Psychology- Folder 2 of 4, 1982-1986, undated (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - NYS Doctoral Project- Psychology- Folder 3 of 4, 1982-1986, undated (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - NYS Doctoral Project- Psychology- Folder 4 of 4, 1982-1986, undated (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - NYS Doctoral Project- Chemistry, History, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Off-Campus Programs, 1975-1977, undated (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Off-Campus Programs, 1978, undated (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Post Secondary Education in Nassau and Suffolk Counties, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Post Secondary Education in New Jersey, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Post Secondary Education in Westchester, 1977, undated (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Northern New Jersey Report, 1977, undated (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Registration Improvement Plan #2- Folder 1 of 2, 1976, 1978-1979, undated (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Registration Improvement Plan #2- Folder 2 of 2, 1976, 1978-1979, undated (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Registration Improvement Plan #1- Folder 1 of 2, undated (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Registration Improvement Plan #1- Folder 2 of 2, 1975, 1976, undated (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Registration Improvement Plan, 1977, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Master Plan, 1982, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Master Plan- State Draft, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    3 1142 04058798 5
  - 1984 Master Plan, 1983-1984, undated (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - 1984 Master Plan Report Background Responses, 1982-1983 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - 1984 Master Plan Report Delegations, 1983, 1984, undated (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - 1982 Master Plan Progress Report (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Master Plan Progress Report- Booklet, 1981, undated (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - 1982 Master Plan Progress Report Deans' Responses (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - 1980 Master Plan Original, 1980, undated (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - 1976 Master Plan Final Copy, 1976, undated (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - 1978 Master Plan Original Final (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - 1982 Master Plan Progress Report- Delegations, 1981-1982, undated (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - 1972 Master Plan Complete, 1971-1972, undated (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - 1972 Master Plan (By School)- Folder 1 of 2, 1971-1972 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - 1972 Master Plan (By School)- Folder 2 of 2, 1971-1972 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - 1974 Master Plan Progress Report, 1973-1975, undated (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - 1974 Master Plan Progress Report Combined, 1973-1974, undated (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - 1974 Master Plan Progress Report Medical Center, 1973-1974, undated (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - 1976 Master Plan Original (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - 1974 Master Plan Progress Report Bulletin- Folder 1 of 2, 1972-1975,undated (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - 1974 Master Plan Progress Report Bulletin- Folder 2 of 2, 1972-1975, undated (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - 1975 Master Plan Progress Report Projections, 1975, undated (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - 1972 Master Plan Progress Report (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - 1976 Master Plan Bulletin Draft, 1974-1975, undated (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - 1975 Master Plan Bulletin- Folder 1 of 2, 1974-1975, undated (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - 1975 Master Plan Bulletin- Folder 2 of 2, 1974-1975, undated (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Manhattanville Finances 1980-1981- Folder 1 of 2, 1979-1981 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    3 1142 04058797 7
  - Manhattanville Finances 1980-1981- Folder 2 of 2, 1979-1981, undated (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Manhattanville Finances 1981-1982 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - 1978 Master Plan Progress Report- complete (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - 1978 Master Plan Progress Report- Complete, 1977-1978 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - 1978 Master Plan Progress Report Bulletin, 1977-1978 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - 1978 Master Plan Progress Report Assignments (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Financial Reports, 1969-1970, 1972, undated (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - NYS Employees in Institutions of Higher Education, 1970-1972, undated (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Regents 1978 Progress Report Bulletin, 1977-1978, undated (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - 1977 Master Plan Progress Report Assignments, 1977-1978 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - 1976 Master Plan Progress Report and Correspondence, 1975-1977, undated (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - 1976 Master Plan Progress Report and Correspondence, 1975-1977, undated (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - 1976 Master Plan Progress Report Bulletin Excerpts (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - 1976 Master Plan Projections, 1975-1976, undated (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - 1976 Master Plan (Box 9, File 16)
  - 1980 Master Plan Delegation of Information, 1979, 1981, undated (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - 1980 Master Plan Bulletin, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - The Regents Tentative Statewide Plan for the Development of Postsecondary Education 1980 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Master Plan 1980 Guidelines and Correspondence, 1979-1980, 1982, undated (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Programs for the 80s - First Draft, Outline, 1979, undated (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - 1980 Master Plan Update - SEHNAP (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Manhattanville Budget Restricted Fund- Folder 1 of 2, 1979-1985 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Manhattanville Budget Restricted Fund- Folder 2 of 2, 1979-1985 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Manhattanville Finances, 1977-1978 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Manhattanville Finances, 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Manhattanville Finances- Folder 1 of 2, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Manhattanville Finances- Folder 2 of 2, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Manhattanville Budget, 1976-1977 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    3 1142 04058795 1
  - Manhattanville Budget, 1977-1978 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Manhattanville Budget- Folder 1 of 2, 1978-1979 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Manhattanville Budget- Folder 2 of 2, 1978-1979 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Manhattanville Budget, 1981-1982 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Manhattanville Budget, 1982-1983 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Manhattanville Budget- Folder 1 of 2, 1980-1981 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Manhattanville Budget- Folder 2 of 2, 1980-1981 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Manhattanville Budget- Folder 1 of 3, 1979-1980 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Manhattanville Budget- Folder 2 of 3, 1979-1980 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Manhattanville Budget- Folder 3 of 3, 1979-1980 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Manhattanville Computers, 1981-1982, undated (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Manhattanville Newsletter, 1978-1980 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - NYU/Manhattanville Joint Computer Science Program, 1978-1981, undated (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Manhattanville/GSAS, 1978-1983, undated (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Manhattanville General, 1981-1982 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Manhattanville College Scholarship, 1977-1978 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Manhattanville General, 1977, undated (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Manhattanville Regents Presentation, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Manhattanville Reports, 1977-1982, undated (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Manhattanville GBA- Folder 1 of 2, 1979-1984, undated (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Manhattanville GBA- Folder 2 of 2, 1979-1984, undated (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Manhattanville Registration of Programs, 1977, undated (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Manhattanville Master Plan Amendments- Folder 1 of 2, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Manhattanville Master Plan Amendments- Folder 2 of 2, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Manhattanville Decentralization, 1980-1983 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Manhattanville Legal Documents 1977, 1976-1977 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Manhattanville Legal Documents 1978, 1977-1978 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Manhattanville Legal Documents 1979, 1979, undated (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Manhattanville Legal Documents 1980-1982, 1978-1980, 1982 undated (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Agreement, 1977, 1980-1981 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Manhattanville General, 1984-1985 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Math Think Survey- Folder 1 of 2, 1983-1984 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Math Think Survey- Folder 2 of 2, 1983-1984 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Middle States Commission- Liberal Education Program, 1982, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - LEP Advisement Survey Spring 1982, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Report to Middle States Association Vol. I: The LIberal Education Program - Copy 1, February 1984 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    3 1142 04058799 3
  - Report to Middle States Association Vol. I: The LIberal Education Program - Copy 2, February 1984 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Report to Middle States Association Vol. I: The LIberal Education Program - Copy 3 (unbound), February 1984 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Value Added: Measuring the Outcomes of Undergraduate Education, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Assessment of NYU Humanities Seminars, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Assessment of NYU Humanities Seminars, March 1978 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Assessment of NYU Humanities Seminars, April 1979 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Assessment of NYU Humanities Seminars, November 1980 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - A Comparative Analysis of the First Three Semesters of NYU Humanities Seminar, April 1979 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Evaluating and Enhancing the Humanistic Perspective of Dental Students, September 1981 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Final Assessment of NYU Humanities Seminars, December 1981 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - A Comparative Analysis of Juniors and Seniors Enrolled in NYU Humanities Seminar, April 1980 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Middle States Assoc. Accreditation Review, 1978, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - State Education Department Middle States Visit- Folder 1 of 2, 1983-1984, undated (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - State Education Department Middle States Visit- Folder 2 of 2, 1983-1984, undated (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Sample LEP Course Proposals - Section II of Self-Study Report, 1981-1983, undated (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Middle States Association 1984 Accreditation Visit, 1983-1984 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Report to the Middle States Association Vol. II: Off-Campus Programs, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Middle States Assoc. Study Abroad Program, 1983-1984 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Middle States Assoc. Study Abroad Program 1985-1986, 1984,1986 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Middle States Assoc. Study Abroad Program, 1984, 1987-1988 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - LEP Mathematics Survey - Student Questionnaires Folder 1 of 2, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - LEP Mathematics Survey - Student Questionnaires Folder 2 of 2 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - A Program for Liberal Education UCC/FAS, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - LEP Tracking System, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - LEP Math Requirement Proposal, 1979-1980, undated (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - LEP Evaluation 1984, 1982-1984, undated (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - LEP Advisement/Scheduling Survey, circa 1983 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - LEP Faculty Ranks, 1981-1983, undated (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - LEP Math Survey, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Foreign Language Survey WSUC, 1982, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - McClellend Measures of Liberal Education, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Attitudes Towards LEP Areas- Fears, 1972, 1975, 1983, undated (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Liberal Education Literature, 1969, 1979-1982, undated (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Tests of General Education- ETS, 1981-1983, undated (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Assessment of General Education at Other Schools- Folder 1 of 2, 1978, 1982-1983 undated (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Assessment of General Education at Other Schools- Folder 2 of 2, 1978, 1982-1983 undated (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Staffing for Skill Areas, 1983-1984, undated (Box 12, Folder 1)
    3 1142 04058796 9
  - CAS Points Distrubtion Study, 1978, undated (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Integrated Core Curriculum Proposal, September 1979 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Preliminary Reports for Study Groups at General Education Conference, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - New Transfers Admitted in 9/80, circa 1980 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Expository Writing Self Study Report, 1982-1983 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - LEP Budget, circa 1983-1984 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Freshman Mentor Program, 1981, circa 1983-1984 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - LEP Foreign Language Course Statistics- Folder 1 of 2, circa 1983 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - LEP Foreign Language Course Statistics- Folder 2 of 2, circa 1983 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Student Majors Fall 1982, circa 1983 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Report of the College Writing Committee- Cornell University, May 1982 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - New Course Enrollment, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Annual Comparisons of CAS Students Changing Majors, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Transcript of LEP Open Forum April 27, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 15)